<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Centralized Climate Control (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.CentralizedClimateControl</packageId>
  <author>ColdToad</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/CentralizedClimateControl</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
      <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/UnlimitedHugs/RimworldHugsLib</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
  This is a continuation of ColdToads excellent mod that is no longer updated:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=973091113

[img]https://raw.githubusercontent.com/emipa606/RimWorld-Wrapper/master/Notice.png[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/GYswkZ7.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://discord.gg/SuhwVpM

Non-Steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/CentralizedClimateControl

Chinese translation:
YangHgRi

Added hidden air-pipes on request and grouped the build-buttons.

--- Original description —-
Centralized Air Cooling/Heating System for RimWorld. Build Large Piped Air Climate Systems away from your buildings.

Rimworld Version: 1.0.0 (Check Github releases for older versions)
Version: 1.5.0

Forum Link[ludeon.com]
Recommended: Steam Guide for Creating a Basic Setup

http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1078768280

Watch this video if you are having issues with the guides. It's a little old, but covers the basic usage of the mod!
Youtube Video Link (BaRKy) https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1tnF4kdAnxk

While there are many alternate mods for Central Heating. This mod adds a new network-like resource (like electricity) Air. The heating/cooling system you will build depends on the number of rooms and the heating/cooling capacity of your air networks.

There are 3 colored pipes available. All can carry any type of air.

Following buildings are added:
- Air Intake Fan: Fans to supply air to the system
- Air Climate Control System: Heat or Cool air to a target temperature
- Air Vents: Vent out the heated/cooled air
- Wall Mounted Air Vents
- Large Intakes and Air Climate Units

Features and Differences (from other mods):

Unified Heating/Cooling System
Heating and Cooling is done by 1 unit, so reduces the need to build coolers and heaters.

Outside (and Far away) Heat Exhaust:
The Heat Exhaust of the Climate Control units isn't located adjacent to rooms. They are located far away from your rooms, thus allowing you to make adjacent rooms to fridge rooms.

Air Network
There is a network-like resource (like electricity) which is generated and consumed which is further dictated by Efficiency of the Network.
1) Flow Efficiency
The rate at which your rooms will cool/heat or maintain heat due to changes in the room temps.
Value: 1 Intake Fan for 3 Rooms

2) Thermal Efficiency
The rate at which your Climate Control units can heat the air. Sudden changes like Cold Snaps or Heat wave will inject very cold or very hot air into your system. Climate Control Units will take care that, but their rate is determined by this Efficiency unit.
Value: 1 Climate Control Unit for 3 Intake Fan

You can always check efficiency of each network at the Vents.

Air Temperature inside Pipes
This mod also deals with the temperature of the air in the Pipe Network.

Can share air without Climate Control units
Intakes take note of the Air Temperature the take in. We can practically make Climate Control-less networks that share the same temperature.
For example:
Multiple Frigdes can be connected together, but only 1 is getting the cooling. The rest just share the air.

Bigger buildings for late game
Build larger Intakes and Climate Units which have about 5x more power than a regular machine.

Pipe Switches
If you have multiple pipes near your vent, You can force it to connect to a specific pipe.

Requires:
[ludeon.com]

Installation:
1) Make sure you enable HugsLib first and before this Mod
2) Enable the Mod in the Mod List

Known Issues:
- Compatibility Issues with Redist.Heat Mod
- Reinstall doesn't work properly (Install and Uninstall works fine.)

Note:
This is my first mod for any game ever. There might be some issues. I wanted to see how the community responds to my mod, and want to work more on it! :)

Thanks if you are trying my mod out!

Authors:
- vasumahesh
- [B19 changes] Jdalt40 [github.com]

Credits:
- carlgraves for "Central Heating" [ludeon.com]
- Redist Heat [ludeon.com]
- Dubs Hygiene Mod [ludeon.com]

License:
MIT License

Alternate Links:
- Google Drive Link [drive.google.com]
POPULAR DISCUSSIONS View All (10)
52 30 Sep, 2019 @ 5:56pm

PINNED: Bugs and Issues
ColdToad
18 29 Nov, 2019 @ 4:59pm

Feature Suggestions
ColdToad
16 24 Dec, 2018 @ 4:21pm

Thoughts, Quirks, Bugs, and Oddities
Mavoc</description>
</ModMetaData>